Guide to the Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Periodicals Collection, 1962-1994 RL.00024
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- ALFA Periodicals Collection, 1972-1994, 47 boxes
  - Fund for Southern Communities Newsletter (Atlanta, Ga.), 1990 March-1991 February (Box 13)
  - Furies (Washington, D.C.), 1972 January-1973 June (Box 13)
  - Future is Female (Florence, Mass.), 1983 April [?] (Box 13)
  - Fuzz Watch (Seattle, Wash.), 1980 November [?] (Box 13)
  - Gaiety (Memphis, Tenn.), 1976 July (Box 13)
  - Gainesville, FL. untitled newsletter (Gainesville, Fla.), 1994 August (Box 13)
  - GAPAC News (Atlanta, Ga.), 1987 (Box 13)
  - Gay Activist, The (New York, N.Y.), 1973 February-1979 July (Box 13)
  - Gay Anarchist (Washington, D.C.), circa 1983 (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders (G.L.A.D.) (Boston, Mass.), 1979 (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (New York, N.Y.), 1988 March-1994 June (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Community Services Center (Hollywood, Calif.), 1987 May-1990 (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Historical Society of Northern California, Newsletter of - Our Stories, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Media Workers Bulletin (Washington, D.C.), 1984 January-1984 June (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Outreach to Elders (GLOE), 1986 March-1990 February (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Parents Coalition International (GLPCI Network), 1992 (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Press Association, 1985 May-1988 September [?] (Box 13)
  - Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund - Victory Newsletter, 1991 December-1992 July (Box 13)
  - Gay Archivist (Toronto, Ontario), 1979 June-1986 June (Box 13)
  - Gay Blade (Washington, D.C.), 1973 April-1973 December (Box 13)
  - Gaybriel (Atlanta, Ga.), 1979 September (Box 13)
  - Gay Clone (New York, N.Y.), 1977 May-1978 May (Box 13)
  - Gay Comix (Princeton, Wis.), 1980 September (Box 13)
  - Gay Community News (Gay Weekly) (Boston, Mass.), 1976 February-1989 September [?] (Box 13-17)
  - Gay Game II, 1986 May-1985 April (Box 17)
  - Gay Iowan, The. (Iowa City, Iowa), 1986 December-1986 November (Box 17)
    University of Iowa
  - Gay - Louisiana: D.O.B. Newsletter (New Orleans, La.), 1976 March-1977 January (Box 17)
  - Gay Liberation News for Florida, 1976 (Box 17)
  - Gay Liberator (Detroit, Mich.), 1973 January-1976 (Box 17)
  - Gay Lutheran: Publication of Lutherans Concerned for Gay People (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1978 August (Box 17)
  - Gay Persons Alliance Newsletter (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1976 April (Box 17)
  - Gay Press Association Newsletter (GPO) (Washington, D.C.), 1983 June (Box 17)
  - Gay Rights Alliance (Atlanta, Ga.), 1977 October (Box 17)
  - Gayly Oklahoman, The (Oklahoma City, Okla.), 1983 November (Box 17)
  - Gaynin' (Denver, Colo.), 1980 May (Box 17)
  - Gays on the Hill (Washington, D.C.), 1977-1978 (Box 17)
  - Gaysweek, 1977 October (Box 17)
  - Gay Youth Community News (San Francisco, Calif.), 1979 August-1984 July (Box 17)
  - Gayzette (Atlanta, Ga.), 1980 December-(?) (Box 17-18)
    [Changed to Gazette, then Metropolitan Gazette]
  - Gaze (Memphis, Tenn.), 1981 January-1990 November (Box 18)
  - GARAL (Georgia Abortion Rights Action League) (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 April-1993 (Box 18)
  - Georgia Advocates for Battered Women and Children, 1994 April (Box 18)
  - Georgia Gay Alliance, 1977 August (Box 18)
  - Georgia Network Against Domestic Violence (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988 May-1989 June (Box 18)
  - Georgia Peace and Justice Report, 1984 September-1985 June (Box 18)
  - Georgia State University Gay Student Alliance, 1988 May-1991 July (Box 18)
  - Georgia State University College of Arts and Sciences: Women's Studies, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Georgians Against Nuclear Energy Ganesayer, 1978 August-1990 (Box 18)
  - Georgia Women's Political Caucus, 1973 October-1984 January (Box 18)
  - Gerber/Hart: Gay and Lesbian Library, 1986 June-1991 June (Box 18)
    [missing: 1987-1990]
  - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club (Washington, D.C.), 1982 January-1983 August (Box 18)
  - Girljock: The Magazine, 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - GLAD (Gay, Lesbian, and Affirming Disciples) Alliance: Crossbeams, 1987 January (Box 18)
  - GLOE, 1989 June (Box 18)
    [see Gay and Lesbian Outreach to Elders]
  - Golden Threads (Quincy, Mass.), 1988 April-1994 July (Box 18)
  - Goodbye To All That (Austin, Texas), 1975 April-1978 January (Box 19)
  - Good Vibes Gazette: Good Vibrations (San Francisco, Calif.), 1989 (Box 19)
  - Gourmet Club Newsletter, 1989 October-1990 September (Box 19)
  - Grand Jury Report (Washington, D.C.), 1977-1980 (Box 19)
    [Changed title to: Grand Jury Washington Bulletin]
  - Grapevine: Newsletter of Lesbian Mothers' Defense (Toronto, Ontario), 1979-1985 (Box 19)
  - Grass Roots, 1979 April-1976 May (Box 19)
  - Gray Panther Network (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1980 January-1980 August (Box 19)
  - Great Speckled Bird, The (Atlanta, Ga.), 1969 April-1985 February (Box 19)
  - Green Mountain Dyke News (Bennington, Vt.), 1980 October-1980 December (Box 19)
  - Grio, 1978 September (Box 19)
  - Guardian (Supplement on Lesbian and Gay Liberation), 1989 (Box 19)
  - Guardian, The, 1992 March-1992 June (Box 19)
  - Guide to the Gay Northeast (Boston, Mass.), 1989 November (Box 19)
  - Habari-Habari (Washington, D.C.), 1981 February-1981 April [?] (Box 19)
  - Hagborn: A Radical Feminist Newsletter (Albany, N.Y.), 1980 (Box 19)
  - HagRag: Intergalactic Lesbian Feminist Press, 1990 March-1991 August (Box 19)
  - Haiti Alert (Miami Beach, Fla.), 1983 May (Box 19)
  - Hamaagal, 1993 May-1994 June (Box 19)
  - Harpie's Monthly (Oakland, Calif.), 1984 June-1984 July (Box 19)
  - Harvey Milk Archives Newsletter, The (San Francisco, Calif.), 1983 January-1983 July (Box 19)
  - Healing Aids: Newsletter of Healing, 1987 December (Box 19)
  - Healthy Closet, The (Atlanta, Ga.), 1978 July-1982 February (Box 19)
  - Hecate (Brisbane QLD, Australia), 1986 (Box 19)
  - Helen Dinet Memorial Women's Center, 1981 July-1982 August (Box 19)
  - Hera (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1975 December (Box 19)
  - Heresies (New York, N.Y.), 1977-(?) (Box 19)
  - Hericane: Gay Coast Women's Network (Gulfport, Miss.), 1989 October (Box 20)
  - Herizon (Florida), 1984 October (Box 20)
  - Her Say (San Francisco, Calif.), 1978 August (Box 20)
  - Homologie (Holland), 1990 March-1990 April (Box 20)
  - Homosexual Counseling Journal (New York, N.Y.), 1974 April-1974 October (Box 20)
  - Homosexual Information Center Newsletter (Bossier City, La.), 1988-1991 (Box 20)
    [missing: 1989-1990]
  - Hopi Epicentre for International Outreach (Chicago, Ill.), 1984 November-1994 January (Box 20)
  - Houston Gay and Lesbian Political Caucus (Houston, Texas), 1988 March (Box 20)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund: Momentum, 1988-1991 (Box 20)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund: Presidential Bulletin, 1992 March-1992 June (Box 20)
  - Hysteria (Kitchener, Ontario), 1980-1982 (Box 20)
  - I Know You Know, 1985 January-1986 April (Box 20)
  - ILIS Newsletter (formerly CLIT 007), 1987 May-1984 December (Box 20)
  - Indian Reader, The (Strawberry Plains, Tenn.), 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Inside the Washington Lobby (Arlington, Va.), dates unknown (Box 20)
  - Integrity Atlanta, 1983 February-1994 July (Box 20)
  - Interchange Resource Center (Washington, D.C.), 1982 January-1982 February (Box 20)
  - International Association of Lesbian and Gay Archives and Libraries (IALGAL Newsletter), 1990 August (Box 20)
  - International Gay Association, 1981 January (Box 20)
  - International Gay Travel Association, 1988 July-1988 August (Box 20)
  - International Lesbian and Gay Association Journal (Washington, D.C.), 1980 (Box 20)
  - International Woman to Woman, The, 1985 December (Box 20)
  - Interracial Books for Children Bulletin, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Interweave (Evanston, Ill.), 1985 (Box 20)
  - Isis International Women's Journal and Supplement (Women in Action) (Rome, Italy), 1984 August [?] (Box 20)
  - Island Lesbians Magazine, 1984 February-1985 June (Box 20)
  - Issues: An AIDS Forum (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1987 (Box 20)
  - Issues on the Journal of Substance for Progressive Women (Forest Hills, N.Y.), 1989 (Box 20)
  - It Ain't Me Babe (Berkeley, Calif.), 1970 May-1970 December (Box 20)
  - Japan Interpreter: Journal of Social and Political Ideas, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Join Hands (San Francisco, Calif.), 1977 February-1977 March (Box 20)
  - Journal of Family Violence (New York, N.Y.), 1986 March (Box 20)
  - Journal of Gay and Lesbian Psychotherapy (Binghamton, N.Y.), 1988 November [?] (Box 20)
  - Journal of Social Issues (Ann Arbor, Mich.), 1972 (Box 20)
  - Journal of Women and Aging, 1989 August [?] (Box 20)
  - Jump Cut (Chicago, Ill.), 1981 (Box 20)
  - Just Like a Women: A Publication of Atlanta, 1970 November (Box 20)
    [photocopy]
  - Kalliope: A Journal of Women's Art (Jacksonville, Fla.), 1984 (Box 20)
  - Knoxville Ten Percent, 1987 April-1987 June (Box 20)
  - Ladder, The, 1962 November-1972 May (Box 20)
    [missing: 1966-1968]
  - Lady-Unique-Inclination-Of-The-Night, 1976-1978 (Box 21)
  - Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1979-1994 (Box 21)
    [missing: 1991-1994]
  - Lambda Rising, 1988-1993 (Box 21)
    [missing: 1990-1991]
  - Lambda Speaks (Jacksonville, Fla.), 1978 March-1978 June (Box 21)
  - L' Androgyne (Montreal, Quebec), 1988 (Box 21)
  - L' Archigai, 1992 November-1993 October (Box 21)
  - Lavender Health, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Lavender Left (New York, N.Y.), 1982 (Box 21)
  - Lavender Life, 1992 February (Box 21)
  - Lavender Tide (Tuscaloosa, Ala.), 1989 August-1990 February (Box 21)
  - Lavender Vision (Cambridge, Mass.), 1971 May (Box 21)
  - Lavender Woman (Chicago, Ill.), 1971 November-1976 July (Box 21)
  - Lazette, 1974 June-1975 August (Box 21)
    [also: 1973 May/June]
  - Leaping Lesbian (Ann Arbor, Mich.), 1977 February-1979 May (Box 21)
  - Le'sbein Formed (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1974 October-1980 April (Box 21)
  - Lesbenpresse (Germany), 1975 February -1975 June (Box 21)
  - Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center (New York), 1985-1994 (Box 21)
    [Divided into: Center Happenings, Center Sports, Center Stage, and Center Voice]
  - Lesbian Archive and Information Centre, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Lesbian Center Journal (Charlotte, N.C.), 1976 October-1976 November (Box 21)
    [see Charlotte Women's Center Newsletter]
  - Lesbian Community Center Newsletter (Baltimore, Md.), 1976 September-1976 December (Box 21)
  - Lesbian Community Project (Portland, Ore.), 1987 July-1992 August (Box 21)
  - Lesbian Connection (East Lansing, Mich.), 1974-1994 August [?] (Box 21-22)
  - Lesbian Contradiction (Seattle, Wash.), 1983 -1994 (Box 22)
  - Lesbian Feminist (New York, N.Y.), 1973 August-1979 (Box 22)
  - Lesbian Feminist Center, 1974 May-1977 January (Box 22)
  - Lesbian Feminist Flyer (Richmond, Va.), 1978 April-1994 June [?] (Box 22-23)
  - Lesbian Feminist Organizing Committee Newsletter (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1979 September-1979 December (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Feminist Union Newsletter (Louisville, Ky.), 1976 September-[?] (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Front, The (Jackson, Miss.), 1975 May-1977 January (Box 23)
  - Lesbian/Gay History Researchers Newsletter (Cambridge, Mass.), 1980-1981 (Box 23)
  - Lesbian/Gay Male Community Services Newsletter (Ann Arbor, Mich.), 1981 April-1982 (Box 23)
    [Formerly: Gay Community Services Newsletter]
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives (New York, N.Y.), 1975 June-1992 June [?] (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Insider/Insighter/Inciter (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1980 August-1986 May (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Jewish Congregation Periodicals, 1981 May-1982 February (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Lifeline (Daytona Beach, Fla.), 1977 June [?] (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Line (Clothespin Fever Press), 1990 February [?] (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Message, 1974 August (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Mothers Resource Network, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Network (Rozelle, Australia), 1988 June-1993 (Box 23)
  - Lesbian Network News, 1980 March (Box 23)
  - Lesbian News, The (Culven City, Calif.), 1978 October-1993 March (Box 23--25)
  - Lesbian News, The (Santa Cruz, Calif.), 1988 February (Box 25)
  - Lesbian Organization of Toronto Newsletter (LOOT) (Toronto, Ontario), 1977 March-1980 May (Box 25)
  - Lesbian Position, A (New Haven, Conn.), 1982 April-1974 July [?] (Box 25)
  - Lesbian Resource Center Newsletter (Seattle, Wash.), 1990 January-1990 May (Box 25)
  - Lesbian Tide, The (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1972 July-1980 May [?] (Box 25)
  - Lesbiana Speaks (Miami, Fla.), 1976 April-1977 January (Box 25)
  - Lesbians for Lesbians, dates unknown (Box 25)
  - Lesbians in Fun Endeavors (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988 July (Box 25)
  - Lesbolehti Torajyva (Helsinki, Finland), 1985 January-1988 February (Box 25)
  - Lexington (KY) Women's Center Newsletter (Lexington, Ky.), 1978 June (Box 25)
  - Leviathan, 1970 May [?] (Box 25)
  - Libera (Berkeley, Calif.), 1973 (Box 25)
  - Liberated Guardian, 1972 March [?] (Box 25)
  - Liberation Theology: Black and Feminist, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Life Defining Network News (Decatur, Ga.), 1979 October-1980 February [?] (Box 25)
  - Literary Xpress, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Little Five Points Community Center, The, 1984 (Box 25)
  - Lone Star Lesbians (Austin, Texas), 1977 November (Box 25)
  - Longest Revolution, The (San Diego, Calif.), 1976 December-1978 October (Box 26)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Services The Center, 1991-1993 (Box 26)
  - Lucy Parsons Women's coalition (Boston, Mass.), dates uknown (Box 26)
  - Luna (or Luna News) (Winston Salem, N.C.), 1990 April-1991 November (Box 26)
  - Madness Network News (San Francisco, Calif.), 1976 June (Box 26)
  - Maedenheap, 1985 (Box 26)
    Womenspace, George Washington University
  - Maine Freewoman's Herald (Brunswick, Maine), 1975 April-1975 May (Box 26)
  - Maine Women's Newsletter (Bangor, Maine), date uknown (Box 26)
  - Maize (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1983-1994 (Box 26)
  - Majority Report (New York, N.Y.), 1973 July-[?] (Box 26)
  - Makara, 1977 (Box 26)
  - Mama Raga (Gainesville, Fla.), 1988 November-1994 April [?] (Box 26)
  - Mammy, 1972 October [?] (Box 27)
  - Margins, 1975 August [?] (Box 27)
  - Matriarchist, The (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1978-1979 (Box 27)
  - Matrices (Minneapolis, Minn.), circa 1978-1985 (Box 27)
  - Matrix - Olympia, Washington (Olympia, Wash.), 1982 May [?] (Box 27)
  - Matrix (Santa Cruz, Calif.), 1978 February-1987 April (Box 27)
    [missing: 1979, 1981, 1982, 1985, 1986]
  - Mattachine New Times, 1975 October (Box 27)
  - MAW: A Magazine of Appalachian Women (Huntington, W. Va.), 1978 March-1978 August (Box 27)
  - Media Report to Women (Washington, D.C.), 1986 May [?] (Box 27)
  - Memphis State University - Center for Research on Women Newsletter, 1983 April-1993 (Box 27)
  - Menamore (Wilmington, N.C.), 1989 June [?] (Box 27)
  - Mekle Woo vs. University of California, 1984 June (Box 27)
  - MetkoFair Housing Services Newsletter, 1984 (Box 27)
  - MCSP Reaching Out (Charlotte, N.C.), 1990 April-1991 September (Box 27)
  - Metropolitan Community Church of Atlanta (Atlanta, Ga.), 1977-1994 (Box 27)
  - Midtowner (Atlanta, Ga.), 1983 April [?] (Box 27)
  - Mighty Isis, The (New York, N.Y.), 1983 March [?] (Box 27)
  - Minnesota Lesbian/Gay Committee of the International Gay Olympic Association (Saint Paul, Minn.), 1983 January-1983 October (Box 27)
  - Momazons, 1993 April-1993 May (Box 27)
  - Momma, 1973 January-1974 (Box 27)
  - Mom's Apple Pie (Seattle, Wash.), 1975 April-1994 [?] (Box 28)
  - Montana Women's Resource (Missoula, Mont.), 1976 (Box 28)
  - Monthly Extract, The (Stanford, Conn.), 1975 April-1978 April (Box 28)
  - Monthly Pause (Jacksonville, Fla.), 1976 August-1977 December (Box 28)
  - Moonstorm (Saint Louis, Mo.), 1976-1983 January (Box 28)
  - Mormons for ERA, 1979 November-1985 (Box 28)
  - Morning Due (Seattle, Wash.), 1983 November [?] (Box 28)
  - Mother Jones (San Francisco, Calif.), 1983 September-1983 October (Box 28)
  - Mother Jones Gazette, 1973 January-1973 March [?] (Box 28)
  - Mother Lode, 1971 January-1972 [?] (Box 28)
  - Mothercot Journal, 1980 May [?] (Box 28)
  - Mother Vision (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1973 October (Box 28)
  - Motive (Methodist Student Movement), 1969 March-[?] (Box 28)
  - Mountain Life and Work: The Magazine of the Appalachian South (Clintwood, Va.), 1974 June (Box 28)
  - Mountain Moving (Evanston, Ill.), 1977 (Box 28)
  - Mountain Womyn's Coalition Newsletter, The (Knoxville, Tenn.), 1984 March-1989 December (Box 28)
  - Moving On (Chicago, Ill.), 1977 September-1982 March (Box 28)
  - Moving Out (Detroit, Mich.), 1974-1977 (Box 28)
    [missing: 1975]
  - Mujeres (Madrid, Spain), 1986 November-December 1978 (Box 28)
    [missing: 1987-1977]
  - National AIDS Network, 1986 June-July (Box 28)
  - NARAL (National Abortion Rights Action League) Newsletter (Washington, D.C.), 1976 November-1987 May (Box 28)
  - "A Newsletter" - National Women's Alliance (Nashville, Tenn.), 1978 September-1994 March (Box 28-29)
  - National AIDS Network - NAN Monitor, 1986 June-1986 December (Box 29)
  - National Alliance of Christian Homosexuals - Saga, 1976 October [?] (Box 29)
  - National Anti-Klan Network Newsletter (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981-1985 (Box 29)
  - National Association for Lesbian and Gay Gerontology - "Making a Difference" (San Francisco, Calif.), 1987-1988 (Box 29)
  - Atlanta NAPWA (National Association of People with AIDS) News, 1991 October-1993 April (Box 29)
  - National Black Women's Health Project Vital Signs, 1985 April-1992 September (Box 29)
  - National Coalition Against Sexual Assault (Houston, Texas), 1984 July-1984 August (Box 29)
  - National Coalition of Black Gays, 1982 July-1985 January [?] (Box 29)
  - National Federation of Career Women (N.F.C.W.), 1991 September-1992 April (Box 29)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force. National Lobby Days report., 1992 (Box 29)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Newsletter (Washington, D.C.), 1988 (Box 29)
  - National Gay Archives (Hollywood, Calif.), 1983 (Box 29)
  - National Gay Task Force: Action Report (It's Time), 1977 October-1981 July (Box 29)
  - National Gay Task Force: Task Force Report, 1981 November-1985 November (Box 29)
  - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, 1987 November-1989 May (Box 29)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Caucus, New Alliance Party Radical and Proud!, 1986 July-1986 October (Box 29)
  - National Lesbian Conference (Decatur, Ga.), 1991 February-1991 March (Box 29)
  - NLFO (National Lesbian Feminist Organization) News (Houston, Texas), 1978 May-1979 November (Box 29)
  - National March on Washington Newsletter, 1987 April-1987 May (Box 29)
  - National Organization for Women (Atlanta, Ga.), 1974 August-1993 [?] (Box 29)
    [missing: 1977-1980]
  - National Organization for Women (Nashville Chapter), 1979 September (Box 29)
  - National Sexual Privacy Challenge Bulletin, 1986 September [?] (Box 29)
  - National Women's Health Report (Washington, D.C.), 1986 March-1986 April (Box 29)
  - National Women's Studies Association Librarian's Task Force, 1984 September-1989 October (Box 29)
    [missing: 1987, 1988]
  - Neighborhood Woman (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1977 November-1977 December (Box 29)
  - Nestle Project, 1979 October (Box 29)
  - New Carolina Woman, 1970 November (Box 29)
  - New Day, A (Washington, D.C.), 1981 January-1981 March [?] (Box 29)
  - New Directions for Women (Westwood, N.J.), 1974-1993 July [?] (Box 29)
    [missing: 1975, 1982-1990]
  - New Light, The (Chicago, Ill.), 1981 May-1982 April [?] (Box 30)
  - News from Women Make Movies, 1988 October-1988 November (Box 30)
  - Newsletter, The. (YWCA) (Durham, N.C.), 1982 April-1994 April [?] (Box 30)
  - Newsletter (Tehran, Iran), 1981 June (Box 30)
  - New Women's Times (Rochester, N.Y.), 1980-1986 [?] (Box 30-31)
  - New York City Star, 1975 March (Box 31)
  - New York City University Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies (CLAGS), 1992 March-1994 (Box 31)
    [missing: 1993]
  - New York Radical Feminist Newsletter, 1975 October-1976 February (Box 31)
  - Nine to Five - Atlanta Working Women / Office Workers Newsletter, 1987 March-1987 December (Box 31)
  - No More Cages (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1981-1985 [?] (Box 31)
  - No More Fun and Games: A Journal of Fun and Games (Cambridge, Mass.), 1968 February-1971 August [?] (Box 31)
  - NCCGLE Notes: Newsletter of the North Carolina Coalition for Gay and Lesbian Equality (Winston Salem, N.C.), 1990 March-1990 October (Box 31)
  - Northwestern University Library Women's Collection Newsletter, 1977-1991 [?] (Box 31)
  - Nuclear Freeze / Jobs with Peace Newsletter: Peace Option (Atlanta, Ga.), 1984-1989 [?] (Box 31)
  - Of a Like Mind (Madison, Wis.), 1985 May-1994 June [?] (Box 32)
    [missing: 1986 -1988]
  - Older Dykes Space Newsletter, 1985 March (Box 32)
  - Older Women's League, 1985 January-1986 January (Box 32)
  - Old Lesbian Organizing Committee Newsletter (Chicago, Ill.), 1991 February-1994 March [?] (Box 32)
  - Olivin Records, 1992 January-1991 February (Box 32)
  - On Our Backs, 1984-1986 (Box 32)
  - On Our Side (Athens, Ohio), 1979 May-1979 June (Box 32)
  - On Parade (San Francisco, Calif.), 1984 April (Box 32)
  - On Target (Uncasville, Conn.), 1989 September-1989 December (Box 32)
  - On the Issues (Forest Hills, N.Y.), 1990-1991 (Box 32)
  - On Track, 1993 April-1993 August (Box 32)
  - ONYX Black Lesbian Newsletter, 1982 December-1984 November (Box 32)
    [missing: 1983]
  - Open Door, The (Salt Lake City, Utah), 1978 September-1978 October (Box 32)
  - Oregon Liberator, 1972 -1973 (Box 32)
  - Organizing Notes (Washington, D.C.), 1983-1984 (Box 32)
  - Other Black Woman, The (Jackson Heights, N.Y.), 1983 [?] (Box 32)
  - Other Woman, The, dates unknown (Box 32)
  - Our Lady's Mission (Austin, Texas), 1982 October (Box 32)
  - Our Own (Norfolk, Va.), 1978 March-1986 September (Box 32)
  - Our Stories, 1993 (Box 32)
  - Our Voice (Eden Prairie, Minn.), 1987 January-1991 December (Box 32)
  - OUT!, 1977 [?] (Box 32)
    [formerly: NEWSWEST]
  - Out and About, 1981 August-1984 March (Box 32)
    [missing: 1982-1983]
  - Outfront: New York City Mayor's Office for the Lesbian and Gay Community, 1989-1991 (Box 32)
    [missing: 1990]
  - Out in Academia - Newsletter of Multicultural Lesbian and Gay Studies, 1985 December-[?] (Box 32)
  - Outlines (Chicago, Ill.), 1988 February-1989 January (Box 32-33)
  - Outlook: National Lesbian and Gay Quarterly (San Francisco, Calif.), 1988-1992 (Box 33)
  - Paid My Dues: Journal of Women and Music (Chicago, Ill.), 1974 April-1980 Spring (Box 33)
  - PAGODA Newsletter (Saint Augustine, Fla.), 1990 April-1990 September (Box 33)
  - Pandora (Seattle, Wash.), 1976 August-1979 November (Box 33)
  - Pan International (Copenhagen, Denmark), 1980 (Box 33)
  - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (Atlanta, Ga.), 1986 February-1988 May (Box 33)
  - Partners: Newsletter for Gay and Lesbian Couples (Seattle, Wash.), 1990 May-1990 June (Box 33)
  - Passion, 1985 -1990 [?] (Box 33)
    [missing: 1991-1993]
  - Pedestal, 1970 July-1971 October (Box 33)
  - Peoples Press, 1976 February (Box 33)
  - Personally (Daly City, Calif.), 1988 January (Box 33)
  - Personal News Monthly Newsletter (Birmingham, Ala.), 1983-1986 December [?] (Box 33)
  - Pflagpole: Federation of Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays, Inc. (Washington, D.C.), 1989 (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia Gay News, 1977 December (Box 33)
  - Pink Trash (Charlotte, N.C.), 1977 May-1977 September (Box 33)
    [formerly: The Free Press]
  - Plains Woman (Grand Forks, N.D.), 1987 March-1988 October (Box 33)
  - Playbill (Atlanta, Ga.), 1984 June (Box 33)
  - Plexus- Bay Area Women's Newspaper, 1974 December-1986 March [?] (Box 33-34)
    [missing: 1985-1977, 1979]
  - Pointblank Times (Houston, Texas), 1975 May-1978 May (Box 34)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund (New York, N.Y.), 1981 July (Box 34)
  - Political Woman (Irvine, Calif.), 1988 [?] (Box 34)